##FIND QUESTIONS AT https://opentdb.com/api_config.php


question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Riot Games 'League of Legends' the name of Halloween event is called "
                 "'The Reckoning'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game 'Until Dawn' Emily is the only playable character "
                 "who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
